Guide to the George Hyde Clarke and Hyde Hall research papers.
Clarke, George Hyde and Hyde Hall research papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
George Hyde Clarke and Hyde Hall research papers.
8439
Kearns, William A.
2.4 cubic feet.
Manuscripts, research materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Notes, copies, tapes, and other files from Kearns' research on the George Hyde Clarke family of Cooperstown, Hyde Hall, their house, and their plantations in Jamaica.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Notes, copies, tapes, and other files from Kearns' research on the George Hyde Clarke family of Cooperstown, Hyde Hall, their house, and their plantations in Jamaica.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kearns, William A.; Clarke family.; Clarke, George Hyde, 1676-; Clarke, George Hyde, 1768-; Hyde Estate (Jamaica); Hyde Hall (Springfield, N.Y.); Swanswick Estate (Jamaica)
Subjects:
Families -- New York (State) -- Otsego County.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collection #2800, George Hyde Clarke Family Papers
CONTAINER LIST
- Tape cassette: PRO – CO441, part of JP2, tr-9891 (Box 1)
- Reel to reel tape recording: Mrs. Fox, tr-9892 (Box 1)
- Reel to reel tape recording: Pulteney ect., tr-9893 (Box 1)
- Reel to reel tape recording: Vouchers – E.B. Marehouse (1826, 1830), other vouchers (1824-1833), little 9 Partners, misc. (1789-1834), tr-9894 (Box 1)
- Reel to reel tape recording: Vouchers (1815-1821), tr-9895 (Box 1)
- Reel to reel tape recording: Bills, receipts, leases (ca. 1804-1830), Cherry Valley leases (1743-1763), tr-9896 (Box 1)
- Reel to reel tape recording: Misc. leases, survey book (1770-1778), account books (1789-1821), 4 Bradt Tract, Quit rent account, tr-9897 (Box 1)
- Reel to reel tape recording: Vouchers (1802-1815), tr-9898 (Box 1)
- Reel to reel tape recording: Clarke manuscript, accounts and leases, tr-9899 (Box 1)
- Reel to reel tape recording: Clark manuscript, Cherry Valley rent accounts, Bradt Tracts rent accounts, field books, tr-9900 (Box 1)
- Part of old map showing Charlotte County, NY, and adjoining NY and VT (Box 1)
- Observations by WAJK on George Clark and value of papers to researchers (Box 1)
- Finished manuscript (Box 1)
- Clark research notes (Box 1)
- Jamaica estates maps (Box 1)
- Rent records (ca. 1797-1821) (Box 1)
- Thesis – outline, notes (Box 1)
- Book of legal cases (Box 1)
- Docs SYR 1-82 through 4-82 (Box 1)
- Rome maps (Box 1)
- Catskill, Bradt’s Tracts (Box 1)
- Little 9 Partners (Box 1)
- N.Y.S. outline maps (Box 1)
- Copies of transcript (Box 1)
- Bibliographic notes, rent receipts, etc. (Box 1)
- Wallumsack and Vermont (1790-1806) (Box 1)
- DeWitt Clinton and Partisanship (1811-1820) (Box 1)
- Long Patent (Box 1)
- Cherry Valley (Box 1)
- Oriskany, Catskil (1790-1806) (Box 1)
- Bradt Tracts (1790-1806) (Box 1)
- Docs #17-1 through 71-12 (Box 1)
- Misc/Clark (Box 1)
- Dennis, Tammy M. (Box 2)
- Book project (Box 2)
- Last will of GHC (Box 2)
- Chapter 1 (Box 2)
- Clark Transcript (Box 2)
- Maps (Box 2)
- Notes (Box 2)
- Micro index (Box 2)
- Docs 1-15 (Box 2)
- Docs 16-30 (Box 2)
- Docs 31-45 (Box 2)
- Docs 46-49 (Box 2)
- Docs 50-105 (Box 2)
- Docs 106-150 (Box 2)
- Docs 151-175 (Box 2)
- Docs 176-202 (Box 2)
- Docs 203-225 (Box 2)
- Docs 226-250 (Box 2)
- Docs 251-285 (Box 2)
- Docs 286-323 (Box 2)
- Docs 324-385 (Box 2)
- Docs 386-408 (Box 2)
- Misc. (Box 2)
- Draft of guide to the George Clark Papers (1981) (Box 3)
- Index of names (Box 3)
- Catskill map (Box 3)
- Letters from/to WAK and Gould Colman (Box 3)
- Clark transcripts (Box 3)